engagebdr.com 2019-12-11

# Privacy Policy – engage:BDR | Branding Driven by Results

Updated as of June 26, 2018

INTRODUCTION

At engage:BDR, LLC privacy is a top priority and we provide this Privacy Policy to outline our practices and procedures with respect to information collection and use to enable you to make an informed decision about sharing information with us when you use our website. engage:BDR, LLC and its associated business units (“engage:BDR” or “we”, “us”, “our”) is an advertising network, which means we may deliver advertisements to other websites you visit and may gather certain information when you visit those websites, as well.

After reviewing the Privacy Policy, if you have any further questions, please contact us at: [privacy@engagebdr.com](mailto:privacy@engagebdr.com)

ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS

engage:BDR, LLC strongly recommends you read this Privacy Policy carefully. This is our official Privacy Policy which forms part of your legal agreement with us. By visiting this website and/or sharing information with us, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy and any Terms and Conditions posted on our website or otherwise linked to herein.

WE CAN MODIFY THIS PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy was last revised on the date at the top of this page. We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to modify, add or delete provisions of this Privacy Policy at any time, and from time to time, by posting updated Privacy Policies on the website. Our posting is the only official and required notice you will receive. Your use of our website after the effective date of any such modification means you accept and agree to be bound by the Privacy Policy, as modified. We urge you to come back to this web page and review this Privacy Policy regularly so that you remain aware of the terms and conditions that apply to you.

INFORMATION ENGAGE:BDR, LLC COLLECTS

_Personal Identifiable Information (PII)_

Personal Identifiable Information is data that can be used directly, or with reasonable effort, indirectly, to contact or identify you, and may include, but is not limited to, your name, phone number, date of birth, age, gender, email address and home address, among other things.

engage:BDR, LLC does not intentionally collect PII from website visitors and takes precautions to avoid the collection of PII. engage:BDR, LLC cannot guarantee it may not inadvertently come into the possession of PII. Additionally, engage:BDR, LLC may obtain PII from our website when you, the website user, choose to provide it to engage:BDR, LLC. Collection of PII may occur when you send us PII about yourself in an email or by completing an online form or registration on our website. PII obtained in this manner may be stored for a reasonable time for record keeping purposes. You are not required to provide any PII to us unless you choose to access features on this site which require the information. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy or other terms of use on this website, then you should immediately exit this website and discontinue using the site.

_Non-Personal Identifiable Information (Non-PII)_

Non-Personal Identifiable Information is information that cannot be used to personally identify the user. As part of our on-going efforts to ensure the best possible experience for all advertising recipients, our technology may use log files, web beacons and cookies to collect data from browsers, advertisers and third party sites to aggregate information. The information collected is used for marketing purposes, enabling us to determine which advertisements perform well, allowing us to more effectively match advertisements and website content to your interests, assisting us in improving the operation of our services, and enabling us to provide general statistics to our business partners and clients regarding use of engage:BDR, LLC’s services.

HOW INFORMATION IS COLLECTED

“Log files” track actions occurring on websites and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, click data and types of advertisements viewed.

“Web beacons” consist of small strings of code that represent a graphic image request on a web page, a page in an online application, or in an email. A graphic image can be associated with the web beacon, but it is not required. When an image is present, usually the image is designed to blend into the background of the web page, application, or email in which it appears. Often a beacon will be placed by an online data collecting company without an image, so it is invisible to the user, and in the smallest discrete space possible on the screen. This is a “pixel” and is essentially an invisible web beacon. Pixels and web beacons can be used for site traffic reporting, unique visitor counts, advertising auditing and reporting, personalization, and other uses. This is  typically done by writing or editing cookies on each user’s computer. Therefore, like cookies, they cannot be used to log keystrokes, copy personal files from your computer, or replicate like a virus.

“Cookies” are files (e.g. HTTP cookies) that are stored on your internet enabled device (which includes your computer, cellular phone or other PDA). Nearly all websites, including ours, use a feature of your internet browser to set a Cookie on your device. The website which places a cookie on your device can then recognize the device when you revisit the site. Cookies are used to improve the experience users have when they see web advertisements and ensure that when a web user clicks on an advertisement, they are sent to the correct click-through destination. We may use Cookies to estimate the total reach of an advertising campaign, as well as frequency of display. This allows advertisers to determine with greater accuracy the composition of the audience they reach. Cookies are also used to control the delivery of a series of advertisements to a web browser, and to limit the number of times a web browser receives any one advertisement. You can turn off all cookies, in case you prefer not to receive them. You can also have your computer warn you whenever cookies are being used. For both options you have to adjust your browser settings (such as Mozilla, Firefox, or Internet Explorer). There are also software products available that can manage cookies for you. Please be aware, however, that when you choose to reject cookies, this choice may limit the functionality of the website you visit and you may lose access to some of its features.

HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

We will only use information we collect or obtain when you use our website, as described in this Privacy Policy, for our internal purposes or to ensure compliance with our Terms and Conditions. If any time in the future, we decide we are going to use your information in a way that differs from our then current Privacy Policy, we will give you notice as described in the section above entitled WE CAN MODIFY THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

SECURITY

Information that engage:BDR, LLC collects is stored on servers that are managed using standard security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information in an effort to protect information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure. Please keep in mind, however, that whenever you give out PII online there is a risk that third parties may intercept and use that information. While engage:BDR, LLC strives to protect your PII and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online. By using this site, you expressly acknowledge and agree that we do not guarantee the security of any data provided to or received by us through this site and that any PII, other data or information received from you through the site is provided to us at your own risk, which you expressly assume.

DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES

engage:BDR, LLC may share non-PII with trusted third  party partners for a variety of reasons, including to enable our platforms or partners to deliver targeted advertisements that we or they believe will be of most interest to you. engage:BDR, LLC may also disclose your personal information to third parties in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. Release of your personal data pursuant to this section, to any person or entity under any circumstances shall be based on a determination made solely by us, exercising our own discretion, permission for which is expressly granted by you to us in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

engage:BDR, LLC may share Non-PII and PII with entities controlling, controlled by, or under common control with engage:BDR, LLC engage:BDR, LLC may transfer information, to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets, bankruptcy, or other corporate change.

Personal Information given to engage:BDR, LLC may be processed by engage:BDR, LLC in all countries in which engage:BDR, LLC operates or in which its affiliates and partners operate. Each of these countries has different privacy laws that afford varying levels of protection for your Personal Information. Regardless of the laws in place in these countries, engage:BDR, LLC will treat the privacy of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. With exception of persons located in the EU and Switzerland, by providing your Personal Information to engage:BDR, LLC, you consent to engage:BDR, LLC’s transmission to, and processing of your information in, any jurisdiction, in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

DISCLAIMERS

The Privacy Policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond engage:BDR, LLC’s control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation. This online Privacy Policy only applies to information collected through this website. This privacy policy does not apply to any information we may collect from you in any place other than this website.

engage:BDR, LLC may provide links to third party websites from our website. Third party websites may utilize a variety of data collection tools to collect visitor data. engage:BDR, LLC is not responsible for the privacy practices, policies or content of third party websites. Please review the privacy policy of individual websites visited to learn more about the collection practices of that website. Even if we have a relationship with a third party you may encounter or see on our website, the advertising, links or references to third parties or any of their websites, including any Cookies or other technology they may use, are not under our control and they have their own terms, conditions, policies and practices that apply to you in connection with their websites, including those concerning collection, use and disclosure of your information.

DATA RETENTION

We will retain your information and the personal information we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [privacy@engagebdr.com](mailto:privacy@engagebdr.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

ACCESS

You have a right to access to your Personal Information and you may update, correct, or delete your account information and email preferences at any time by logging-in to your account and changing the information on file or by e-mailing engage:BDR, LLC at [privacy@engagebdr.com](mailto:privacy@engagebdr.com) with your request. To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting Users profile access. Similarly, if you’ve provided us with PII via the Websites, you may send us an email at [privacy@engagebdr.com](mailto:privacy@engagebdr.com) and we will respond within a reasonable time.

OPTING OUT

You can opt out of having engage:BDR, LLC collect your Non-PII by clicking on the opt-out link below. engage:BDR, LLC offers an “opt-out Cookie” to block the placement of future engage:BDR, LLC Cookies. If you have multiple internet browsers or users on the same computer, you will need to perform the opt-out operation for each browser and/or user. If you or your privacy software deletes the opt-out Cookie from your computer, you will need to repeat the process.

Please note that the above link for an opt-out Cookie is only applicable to the engage:BDR, LLC company website. Please report any problems related to the opt-out process to [privacy@engagebdr.com](mailto:privacy@engagebdr.com).  Through our services and platform, our users have access to services provided by third party companies with whom we have partnered to assist in delivering more relevant ads. If you would like to learn more about the practices of some of the companies we have partnered with, or to obtain further information on Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) consumer opt out services click on the link provided.

If you register on or with our website, you are agreeing and consenting to receive information and updates about your use of our website or our services for which you register. You may opt out of receiving any or all of these communications by following the unsubscribe instructions we will include in each email we send you.

CHANGING OR DELETING YOUR INFORMATION

We may provide you with a mechanism to allow and enable you to correct or update the PII in our current records that we have obtained from you. You can always review and change your PII by contacting us by email at [privacy@engagebdr.com](mailto:privacy@engagebdr.com). Certain PII may not be changed without authentication (e.g., birth date) and you may be asked to provide additional information to allow us to confirm your identity in order to change those. If you ask us to remove your PII, we still reserve the right to retain as much of your PII and for so long as necessary to comply with our legal, regulatory, internal audit and record-keeping requirements.

CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

engage:BDR, LLC adheres to the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. engage:BDR, LLC is very sensitive to the issue of the privacy rights of children. engage:BDR, LLC websites and services generally are neither developed for, nor directed at, children. If we are made aware that we have received information from children under the age of 13, in the absence of verifiable parental consent, we will immediately remove that information from our records.

YOUR REPRESENTATIONS

YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT ANY DISPUTE OVER PRIVACY IS SUBJECT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND APPLICABLE SITE TERMS AND CONDITIONS. You also agree that you have provided notice to, and obtained consent from, any third party individuals whose information you supply to us with regard to: (a) the purposes for which such third party’s information has been collected; (b) the intended recipients or categories of recipients of the third party’s Information; (c) which of the third party’s data are obligatory and which data, if any, are voluntary; and (d) how the third party can access and, if necessary, rectify the data held about them.

CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have any questions or comments regarding this Policy, please contact engage:BDR, LLC’s Data Protection Officer by mail or e-mail as follows:

engage:BDR Data Protection Officer 9220 Sunset Blvd., Suite 100 West Holywood, CA 90069 Email: [privacy@engagebdr.com](mailto:privacy@engagebdr.com)

RIGHT TO LODGE A COMPLAINT WITH A SUPERVISORY AUTHORITY

If you wish to lodge a complaint regarding our use or collection of your personal information, please contact engage:BDR, LLC’s Data Protection Officer at the address above. When we receive formal written complaints, we will contact the person who made the complaint to follow up. We will work with the appropriate supervisory authority, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that we cannot resolve with you directly.

engage:BDR, LLC is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) and/or the Department of Transportation.

engage:BDR, LLC commits to cooperate with EU data protection authorities (DPAs) and comply with the advice given by such authorities with regard to human resources and non-human resources data transferred from the EU.

engage:BDR, LLC complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States. engage:BDR, LLC has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, engage:BDR, LLC commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact engage:BDR, LLC at:

engage:BDR Data Protection Officer 9220 Sunset Blvd., Suite 100 West Holywood, CA 90069 Email: [privacy@engagebdr.com](mailto:privacy@engagebdr.com) Please note that if your complaint is not resolved through these channels, under limited circumstances, a binding arbitration option may be available before a Privacy Shield Panel
